# Ryan Jonah

### Software Developer

With a lifelong passion for technology and years of experience assisting customers through a myriad of different issues, this dedicated problem solver is willing to face every new prospect with an adamant determination towards finding solutions.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### Cloud5, Minto, NB— Customer Service Representative

January 2017 - August 2020 January 2014 - February 2015

- Selling, creating, and canceling hotel reservations across multiple accounts covering hundreds of properties internationally.
- Helping customers resolve issues via phone and email by way of information gathering, internal systems processing, reviewing hotel and company policies, and consulting hotel staff directly.
- Assisting customers with billing inquiries while following Payment Card Industry (PCI) compliance.
- Assisting other call center representatives through escalation calls while fulfilling the rotational role of shift supervisor.
- Assisting customers through the navigation of various hotel websites.
- Assisting other call center representatives in troubleshooting technical issues.

### **EDUCATION**

## **NBCC,** Moncton, NB— Web and Mobile Application Development

September 2020 - June 2021

**Coder Foundry,** Kernersville, NC— Coding Bootcamp

June 2021 - September 2021

**Chipman Forest Avenue School,** Chipman, NB— *High School Diploma* 

June 2011

### References

References available upon request

43 Harts Lake Road Gagetown, NB E5M 1L7 (506) 327-5298 ryan c jonah@yahoo.ca

LinkedIn Github

### **SKILLS**

C#

ASP.NET

**Entity Framework** 

Visual Studio

HTML

**CSS** 

**Javascript** 

React

Git

Python

LINQ

MS SQL Server

Windows OS

Linux OS

Bash

**Customer Service** 

Sales

### **LANGUAGES**

English

### **Hobbies**

Technology, fitness, writing, philosophy, science, history, music, cooking, video games